import 'package:flutter/material.dart';
import 'package:qs_app/components/mcqs_content_box.dart';

class OtsMathContentScreen extends StatelessWidget {
  @override
  Widget build(BuildContext context) {
    return Scaffold(
      appBar: AppBar(
        title: Text('OTS Math'),
      ),
      body: SingleChildScrollView(
        child: Padding(
          padding: EdgeInsets.all(20.0),
          child: Column(
            children: [

              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What should be done to make the coefficient of x2 equal to 1 in 3x2 +7x = 0?',
                option1: 'Multiply the equation by 1/3',
                option2: 'Add 1/3 in both sides',
                option3: 'Divide the equation by 1/3',
                option4: 'Subtract 1/3 from both sides',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Sentences involving the Sign…… between two algebraic expressions are called equations?',
                option1: '<',
                option2: '< or >',
                option3: '>',
                option4: '=',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Two linear factors of x2 – 15x +56 are?',
                option1: '(x+7)and(x-8)',
                option2: '(x-7)and(x-8)',
                option3: '(x-7)and(x+8)',
                option4: '(x+7)and(x+8)',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The number of real roots of the equations |x|2-5|x|+6=0, is?',
                option1: '1',
                option2: '2',
                option3: '3',
                option4: '4',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Solution set of equation 25x2 -1 =0 is?',
                option1: '{±1}',
                option2: '{1/±5}',
                option3: '{1/±7}',
                option4: '{1/±3}',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'An equation of the type 3x +32-x + 6=0 is a/an………?',
                option1: 'Exponential equation',
                option2: 'None of these',
                option3: 'Radical equation',
                option4: 'Reciprocal equation',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The equation x- 2/x-1 = 1-2/x-1 has?',
                option1: 'No solution',
                option2: 'Two solutions',
                option3: 'Threeo solutions',
                option4: 'One solutions',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'If y = 2x and 8y = 1, then x = …………….?',
                option1: '1/8',
                option2: '8',
                option3: '3',
                option4: '-3',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'An equation of the form 22x-3,2x+5=0 is called a/an___ equation?',
                option1: 'Exponential',
                option2: 'reciprocal',
                option3: 'Radical',
                option4: 'All',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The standard form of the quadratic equation is ax2 + bx +c = 0 where a, b,c are……?',
                option1: 'Rational numbers',
                option2: 'Whole numbers',
                option3: 'Irrational numbers',
                option4: 'Real numbers',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Number of way to solve quadratic equation are?',
                option1: '4',
                option2: '3',
                option3: '2',
                option4: '1',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What is the degree of quadratic equation?',
                option1: '4',
                option2: '3',
                option3: '2',
                option4: '5',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The number of root of a quadratic equation is?',
                option1: '6',
                option2: '7',
                option3: '4',
                option4: '3',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Standard form of quadratic equation?',
                option1: 'ax2+ bx + c = 0',
                option2: 'ax2= bx , a ? 0',
                option3: 'ax2 = 0 , a = 0',
                option4: 'b +c = 0 , b ? 0',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The common solution of the quaderatic equations x2-7x+10=0 and x2-10x+16=0 is?',
                option1: '-2',
                option2: '2',
                option3: '3',
                option4: '5',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The solution set of equation 5x2 = 30 x is ……?',
                option1: '{5,30}',
                option2: '{0,-6}',
                option3: '{0,6}',
                option4: '{5,0}',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Solution set of equation 4x2 – 16 = 0?',
                option1: '{2}',
                option2: '{±4}',
                option3: '{4}',
                option4: '{±2}',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'How many linear factors a quadratic equation has?',
                option1: '3',
                option2: '4',
                option3: '5',
                option4: '6',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The factors of x2-8x-20 are?',
                option1: '(x-10)(x+2)',
                option2: '(x-5)(x+4)',
                option3: '(x+10)(x-2)',
                option4: '(x+5)(x-4)',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'An equation of the form 2x4-3x3+7x2-3x+2=0 is called a/an?',
                option1: 'Radical equation',
                option2: 'Reciprocal equation',
                option3: 'Exponential equation',
                option4: 'All',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'If x = ey, then y = logeX= ln x, is known as the _____________ of x?',
                option1: 'Exponential',
                option2: 'Common lagarithmic',
                option3: 'Natural logarithmic',
                option4: 'All',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Let f(x) = x3+ sin x, then f(x) is?',
                option1: 'An even function',
                option2: 'A constant function',
                option3: 'An odd function',
                option4: 'Neither even nor odd',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'For any set X, a function 1 : X?',
                option1: 'An identity function',
                option2: 'An additive identity function',
                option3: 'Quadratic function',
                option4: 'Biquadratic function',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'A unit vector vector is defined as a vector whose magnitude is?',
                option1: 'Unity',
                option2: 'Less than 1',
                option3: 'More than 1',
                option4: 'Zero',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'A vector whose magnitude is unity called?',
                option1: 'Constant vector',
                option2: 'Unit vector',
                option3: 'Null vector',
                option4: 'Zero vector',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Magnitude of the vector V = [3,-4]?',
                option1: '3',
                option2: '4',
                option3: '5',
                option4: '6',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Two non-zero vectorsa & b are parallel ifa x b=?',
                option1: '0',
                option2: '1',
                option3: '-1',
                option4: '–bxa',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'j . k x i equals?',
                option1: 'j',
                option2: 'k',
                option3: 'i',
                option4: 'k.j',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Two non-zero vectors u and v are perpendicula if and only if u.v is equal to?',
                option1: '2',
                option2: '3',
                option3: '4',
                option4: '5',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The dot product of unit vector i with unit vector j is?',
                option1: '0',
                option2: '1',
                option3: '2',
                option4: '3',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
            ],
          ),
        ),
      ),
    );
  }
}


